Okay, hopefully.
I'm just going to make sure that it's
following.
Ohh.
science.
I hate this pun because it always gets
like ink on my hand because I'm not
standing.
So the goal of this interview is to like
get an idea of how do you study.
So this is going to be like semi
structured.
If I feel like you're drifting too far
away from the like questioning topics,
I'm going to drag you back in.
But don't hesitate to tell me what's on
your mind and obviously.
It's okay if you say, yeah,
I kind of don't study most of the time.
That's entirely okay.
Don't lie to make up things.
That's very important.
I'm going to be writing a few notes so I
can call back to your like experiences.
It I guess helps if I can add context to
my questions.
As I'm sure you read in the brief,
I'm here to interview you.
It's going to take 20 minutes or so.
We can overrun a little bit,
but I have another person at 1130,
so you got 24 minutes, should be fine,
I think.
If I ask you a question and you don't
feel comfortable answering,
please just say, yeah,
I don't want to answer that.
It's completely okay.
You can also request to have this deleted
if you feel like I've misrepresented you
or asked you like really tough questions
that make you feel like badly afterwards.
But outside of that,
it is going to be transcribed.
Don't worry, guys, it's gonna be chill,
so I'm gonna give you a really easy
starter question and get you into the
rhythm. So,
what modules do you have this semester?
Yeah, name all of these and your design.
Mechatronics.
Yes, electronics. Electronics? Yes. Okay.
It was sequence of communication.
Ifaz most.
Try to think about data analysis.
So, having engineering societies.
In here.
That's a pretty heavy course load.
It's a lot of courses.
Could you tell me which one you thought
was the most difficult?
Say, they knows some communication. OK,
yeah, that's fine.
Do you want to rank the rest of them,
electronics, electronics, engineering,
design, data analysis? Yeah,
that was tough. OK.
Design, engineer design, yeah,
understandable, and then...
Mhm.
Think about mechatronics, electronics,
math, and engineer and society.
Engineering society,
that could be the biggest one. Yeah, okay,
so that's #7, I guess.
And what do you have with electronics?
Math, electronics, mechatronics.
Mechatronics.
Okay.
I think maybe Touraj has to be the high
school, yeah, OK, so that's one, sure,
and then this one will be two.
Or, and then electronics math,
and it creates...
Like, yeah, next alright, lovely. OK.
How would you say, like,
what would you say influenced the rating?
Like,
think about this in the context of the
toughest one was really tough because we
had to do a lot of maths or physics or a
lot of writing or a lot of reading.
So what influences what where you rank
them?
I want it high because there was stuff
that I didn't know. Or what kind of stuff?
Is it like the maths that was taught,
the physics? Physics. Right, okay.
But what specifically in physics?
Let's dig a little deeper. Like,
was it the equations?
Was it applying the equations?
I was applying the correct formulas into
the context of the diagrams. Right.
So you get a diagram and then you've got
to choose which formula to apply to it.
Yes, it's like different contexts. Yeah,
contextual. Yeah, that makes sense. Okay.
Too.
That makes sense. I mean, honestly,
it's it's like to do with the real world.
So you've got to think about, OK,
So what's it actually doing, right? Yeah.
OK,
I'm gonna move on to some of the main
topics now.
I want to know if you structured your day
around studying like,
do you say from 4 to 6:00 PM I'm gonna
study one subject or I'm gonna study two
subjects and I'm gonna block it in like
one hour block.
Do you do that kind of stuff? No,
but if there's a project, then I would,
but Jen was studying the door.
Right, okay, that makes sense.
Is Moodle integral to like the plan of
your study? Yes, it is. So...
Dig a little bit more, why is it integral?
Like,
what do you use Moodle for specifically?
Yeah, tutorial sheets, action books,
right, tutorial sheets.
So let your notes by that you mean the
slides, right?
And you're just taking notes, I guess.
Yeah, that makes sense. OK.
How do you prioritise your study times?
Do you prioritise your study time? No,
you just kind of do whatever you feel
like or? Yeah,
but when it comes to like exams.
Then I would study here.
Yeah, OK, let's talk about that.
That's actually perfectly fine.
This exam kind of force you into it,
right?
So how do you prioritise for your exams?
You do it deadline based or.
So if the first exam comes up and always
study for that specific. Yeah,
deadline based. OK, yeah, sure.
It's like the next day of the exam,
you just feel the pressure to go. Yeah,
I guess that.
Let's say you have like an easy exam
coming up.
Do you spend less time than you would if
it's like really tough exam coming up?
It's when you say it's profound to how
difficult you find the module, yeah?
Um,
is that because like it requires extra
effort or you feel like it requires extra
effort or? Yeah, probably that, uh,
I would do like a mock. Yeah,
I would do a mock.
Hey, call reporting all of them.
Sorry, I'll do it like a book paper,
just like see where I'm at,
and then if I did good,
then I'll do I'll done less with that
stuff. OK, sure,
so it's like you take a walk,
you gauge how good you are. OK, yeah,
like a like a diagnostic test. Yeah, yeah,
absolutely. Yeah, I get that.
That's actually great.
That's exactly what I'm looking for.
Um...
So do you have different strategies per
module?
Let's say you get a decent grade on your
mocks on both of them.
Do you study in the same way for all of
your modules? Like for instance,
do tutorial sheets? Yeah, I think, yeah,
I do the same way tutorial sheets. OK,
so tutorial sheets are like integral
towards your study plan. Yeah.
Do you use like third party systems like?
For instance, asking, hey,
I'm having an exam in some topic like
electronics. Can you help me?
Can you help ask me some questions so I
can cheque my knowledge? I do use AI,
but I would put some work if they didn't
have the answers or they didn't have
explanations to also that to AI.
You get the worked examples, right? Yeah,
OK.
NAVYA.
Or.
Actually, yeah,
I know exactly what you mean. Like,
that's why when we started,
when I was tutoring,
or like when I was teaching earlier in
the year,
like first semester for that module,
I was doing all of the work by hand,
showing the steps,
because sometimes the tutorial sheets
just don't have steps and you're just
like, what's this? Exactly.
And you don't get to any of the learning,
like the intermediary steps. OK,
do you use any other tools for setting?
Do you like watch YouTube videos?
I'll say yes.
Really,
but as if I don't understand it
completely.
YouTube videos are.
There's always like some Indian guy who's
just got it on. Yeah.
Any other things like for instance,
creating flashcards online? No, it's just.
Which, which,
which formula would you use in this
scenario? No. Okay, fair enough.
There are like online quiz generators
that I've seen as well. You use those.
So it's just, okay, cool,
that makes sense.
Do you have your study materials easily
accessible? Like, it's on Moodle, sure,
but do you download them onto like a
shared folder or? Yeah.
I mean, I get it and then download it.
Yeah.
And then do you happen to like folders in
your computer,
like organised or do you just click on
Google every time? No,
but I do have folders for like different
projects,
but that's mainly for like projects and
other stuff related to that,
not for like exams. Right. OK.
So the exams is just like read the slides,
take some notes,
and then mocks and tutorial sheets. Yeah.
Okay, cool.
How do you feel about Moodle's offerings
when it comes to structuring your study
materials?
Like you've noticed each teacher will,
or each professor will,
organising materials in a different way.
Yeah, exactly. Like,
do you feel like that's a nice way to
study?
Just say one professor lays it out in one
way, another one lays it out in another.
I don't really see a difference. Really?
OK, fair enough. That's fine. Yeah.
They have my lectures in one tab,
two tools in one tab, vision in one tab.
Oh, I see. OK.
And would you say that the revision
material is sufficient normally?
I would say it's okay. It's okay.
Do you want more of the higher quality?
What are you looking for? What's missing?
To toys with answer that, like,
what top examples, yeah.
That makes sense, yeah. I mean,
then you just plug it into an AM,
and then sometimes it gets it wrong,
right? Like the work is on, yeah,
just like, oh my god,
and the other type of the, exactly,
it's AM all the way down.
Okay, so yeah,
we've talked about your study structure.
I want to talk a little bit about like
your study environment. So when you study,
where is it? Is that phone? Yeah, phone.
Yeah, that phone? Like your room?
Do you study like the dining table or
just in your room? Yeah.
A written computer.
Anywhere else, like, for instance,
in the library, you need.
OK, fair enough. OK,
so what makes a good study space? Like,
yes, it's your room, but OK, tidy,
clean and tidy. Yeah, OK.
ID.
Yeah, I agree. I mean,
if you got a lot of clutter,
it can just distract you, right?
Do you find yourself the most productive
when it is clean and tidy? Yeah.
So what are the most important things
other than tightness?
Environment, yeah, as in like,
is it what if it's really noisy?
It's like, yeah, I was like, yeah, OK,
it's cleaning.
Tse.
What about, I mean,
do you live with your family? Yeah. Yeah,
so if your family come in, distractions,
distractions, right? You don't like that,
I'm guessing. Uh, yeah. I mean,
if let's say, I mean,
what if your parents was like a bit of
food for you to eat?
Do you like to have something to snack on
while your reading, while your studies?
It depends if I'm like focused, you know,
like busy, like writing something,
and I'll close me then I'll just chunk,
right?
So you don't like the context switches.
OK, excellent. Yeah.
So, you've said, like,
you need the room to be tidy, silent,
lack of distractions.
Is access to technology important?
Do you need your computer to study?
Would you say? Yeah. Why is that?
Is it because you need to access to? Yeah,
to access it too. Okay, yeah.
Is it difficult to get everything set up
to study? Like,
sometimes if you come home and you're
just like...
I really don't want to study because like
my desk is messy or whatever.
Does that happen to you?
No, no, because of my this is messy.
It's sometimes difficult to. Yeah, sure.
Okay. Can I dig a little bit into that?
Like,
why would you feel not motivated to study?
Like what would you go study?
Like, yeah,
why would you not feel motivated?
Because the exams, exams are made. Yeah,
so you got time, but for the exams,
you're just like, ah,
I can do it tomorrow. Yeah, okay.
I guess last week.
That's entirely fine, not up to you. OK,
so if your motivation is low,
I guess when deadlines are coming up,
you feel the pressure and that's when you
start doing more work. OK, sure, yeah.
I'm going to go to the next topic.
Will you say that you get distracted
often when you're studying?
Sometimes. Do you tell your well?
I'm assuming that if your family is
tracking you,
do you tell them I'm gonna study for the
next hour or so? No.
I actually helped run through this. Or,
you know,
studying at weird hours like 10 to 12 PM.
Nobody's doing anything. Yeah. No,
I don't really like stuff studying our
life.
Nine-ish,
because I wanna get my sleep schedule
right, 9 P.m. or 9 A.m.
But I, I think I ended at about here,
and I do my stuff at 10:00. I was right,
OK. That makes sense. Yep, OK.
When you study,
do you study alone with others,
sometimes with others?
Mostly alone or always alone?
I'll say that. OK,
so you're mostly an alone person.
That's fine. I mean,
I think most people are,
especially in STEM.
So you prefer to study alone,
but you have experience with others.
Why do you prefer to study alone or do
you like it with them?
Because sometimes when it's with others.
Um,
they don't mean provided shut to tobox
them, right? OK,
so there I can shake the topic away from
studying, that makes sense, yeah.
Do you study with others like in a shared
space or in online or?
Sometimes it can be online when it's
nearer to the exams. Yeah, okay.
Is that like on Discord? Yeah, okay.
So I guess you just get into a call,
you do something like pause papers,
you're like, hey,
so I'm getting this wrong.
Can somebody walk me through it? Yeah,
okay. Yeah.
Um...
When you study with others,
how do you coordinate that?
Do you say like at everyone,
we're gonna have a study session in an
hour or? Yeah,
but sometimes I have one person that
doesn't come,
they'll be like three people in total.
Yeah, that's still three brains.
Three brains is better than one.
Unless they get distractions. Yeah.
Okay, do you have your computer with you?
Okay, that's fine.
I'm gonna ask you to walk me through like
a study session. Like,
imagine we've got an exam coming up.
They offer tomorrow. Yeah.
So I want you to talk me through your
thought process.
Let's say it's for your mechatronics exam
because that's really tough.
So lay the scene out for me. Yeah, it's,
I'm gonna say we're in your room. It's.
6pm, you've just had dinner.
You decided to study,
walk me through your thought process two
days from now.
So, let's go to my computer. Yeah.
Open up, and then...
Of open up tutorials and what could what
people then do.
So you're doing a mock paper, right?
You've picked specifically one of the
mocks. Have you done any mocks before now?
Let's say this is 2 days out.
Will this be the first time you're
opening Moodle for a mock exam? Yeah,
okay.
And then we can see that I went to the in
person or revision session. Yeah.
Okay,
so we picked products because it's tough.
Let's say you do poorly on this mock that
you've done.
You score something like a 40% and you're
just like, oh no, what now?
How do you progress from there?
Let's say you've really struggled on the..
.
Control systems part of it, yeah.
How do you do that? What do you do?
focus on the control systems. Yeah, okay,
so what does that entail?
Next weekend.
Tse.
Yeah, what about a tutorial sheet?
Would you go through that again?
Would you plug that into like an AI,
ask it for more questions? Yeah, yeah,
okay.
Would you use any other third party tools
like to help you with recall?
Maybe YouTube, yeah, yeah,
YouTube's great third party tool.
So now you've done another multi set.
Your score has increased.
Say it's at 65 ish.
Are you satisfied with that or do you
want to push a little bit harder? Yeah,
cool. Try to get high.
Let's say there's like 3 multi exams.
So you want to try and get.
At what point will you say you're happy
with how you've studied?
The Sunday, like,
at what point would you say, OK,
I've done all that I could,
and I've finished everything I could like
to tools and OK, yeah, and then...
When you finish all of them and you feel
like you got that,
that's when you feel ready for the exam,
would you say? Yeah. Okay,
that makes sense.
I'm going.
Thank you for your time and your
participation,
but I would like to ask one more thing.
Is there anything else that we haven't
really covered about your study habits
that you feel like you would like to
share with me?
No, that's everything. Yeah. OK. Yeah.
Thank you for your time. Thanks.
Stop the recording.
Ohh.